<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security on timerring</title><link>https://blog.timerring.com/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on timerring</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:52:30 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.timerring.com/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Openssl Overview</title><link>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/the-openssl-overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:52:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/the-openssl-overview/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Overview of Security</title><link>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/the-overview-of-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 20:42:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/the-overview-of-security/</guid><description>&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, security is paramount. As we increasingly rely on technology for communication, commerce, and data storage, understanding the fundamentals of security becomes essential. This article provides an overview of key security concepts, including encryption, digest algorithms, and digital signatures. By exploring these topics, we aim to equip you with the knowledge to protect your digital assets and ensure the integrity and confidentiality of your information. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a tech enthusiast or a professional in the field, this guide will offer valuable insights into the mechanisms that safeguard our digital world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GPG 101</title><link>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/gpg-101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 20:26:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/gpg-101/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>GnuPG is a complete and free implementation of the OpenPGP standard as defined by RFC4880(also known as PGP). GnuPG allows you to encrypt and sign your data and communications; it features a versatile key management system, along with access modules for all kinds of public key directories. GnuPG, also known as GPG, is a command line tool with features for easy integration with other applications.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>This article I will introduce the basic usage of GPG.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>