<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Linux on timerring</title><link>https://blogs.timerring.com/tags/linux/</link><description>Recent content in Linux on timerring</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:38:50 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blogs.timerring.com/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vim Cheatsheet</title><link>https://blogs.timerring.com/posts/vim-cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:38:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blogs.timerring.com/posts/vim-cheatsheet/</guid><description>&lt;p>Vim is a powerful command-line text editor that&amp;rsquo;s been around for decades, and it&amp;rsquo;s still widely used today. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re SSH-ing into a remote server or just prefer the keyboard-centric workflow, Vim is often the go-to choice. The learning curve can be steep at first — I remember the first time I opened Vim and couldn&amp;rsquo;t even figure out how to quit. But once you get the hang of it, the efficiency gains are real. This cheatsheet covers the essentials I use most often, and I’m trying to condense them.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Further Understanding of Proc</title><link>https://blogs.timerring.com/posts/further-understanding-of-proc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 20:49:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blogs.timerring.com/posts/further-understanding-of-proc/</guid><description>&lt;p>The &lt;code>/proc&lt;/code> in Linux is a kind of Pseudo file system (also known as Virtual File System), what it saves is a series of special files that store the current running state of the kernel, and the user can check the hardware info and the runnning processes via the files, even adjust some files to change the state of running kernel. The files in &lt;code>/proc&lt;/code> will be refresh in RAM, so the files&amp;rsquo; size is 0 bytes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Iftop</title><link>https://blogs.timerring.com/posts/the-iftop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:57:06 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blogs.timerring.com/posts/the-iftop/</guid><description>&lt;p>I frequently use &lt;code>ifconfig&lt;/code> and &lt;code>cat /proc/net/dev&lt;/code> to examine network information. However, today, my cloud server crashed unexpectedly. I reached out to the cloud support for assistance. The engineer utilized &lt;code>iftop&lt;/code> to analyze the situation. After the issue was resolved, I started to consider using this tool. Now, let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at this powerful utility.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>