<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CDN on timerring</title><link>https://blog.timerring.com/tags/cdn/</link><description>Recent content in CDN on timerring</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:52:52 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.timerring.com/tags/cdn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloudflare Warp</title><link>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/cloudflare-warp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:52:52 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/cloudflare-warp/</guid><description>&lt;p>Frankly speaking, the first time I heard about Cloudflare is the service so called Cloudflare WARP which is provided by Cloudflare. Nowadays, you must have heard the fastest and private network can be provided by Cloudflare. If I say Cloudflare achieves the fastest object by the first step to visiting any website, the world’s fastest public DNS &lt;code>1.1.1.1&lt;/code>. You can probably guess the private provider, yes, that is Cloudflare &lt;code>WARP&lt;/code>. So this article I will introduce the Cloudflare WARP further zero trust and how to use it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The principle of Cloudflare SaaS Optimization</title><link>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/the-principle-of-cloudflare-saas-optimization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:23:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.timerring.com/posts/the-principle-of-cloudflare-saas-optimization/</guid><description>&lt;p>In common situation, when you use the cloudflare to resolve your domain name, and you choose to use the &lt;code>cloudflare proxy&lt;/code>(the yellow cloud icon), then cloudflare would probably get your domain resources into their CDN, that could be a good thing, but as we know, the network in mainland has some special rules, so for the free tier user, the access to the resources in the CDN would be somehow worse, even &lt;code>rest&lt;/code>. That means, if the user connect to the node which has high latency, the request will experience worse. So this article will introduce some methods to help your resources access to the cloudflare nodes which are optimized for the mainland.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>